[
    {
      "question": "In which film did Black Widow first appear?",
      "correct_answer": "Iron Man 2",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Avengers", "Captain America: The First Avenger", "Iron Man"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the AI created by Tony Stark that eventually becomes The Vision?",
      "correct_answer": "J.A.R.V.I.S.",
      "incorrect_answers": ["F.R.I.D.A.Y.", "Ultron", "E.D.I.T.H."]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Infinity Stone is hidden inside the Eye of Agamotto?",
      "correct_answer": "The Time Stone",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Mind Stone", "The Soul Stone", "The Space Stone"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the real name of the Winter Soldier?",
      "correct_answer": "Bucky Barnes",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Sam Wilson", "Clint Barton", "Steve Rogers"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Peter Quill's first spaceship in Guardians of the Galaxy?",
      "correct_answer": "The Milano",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Benatar", "The Quinjet", "The Starblaster"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the main villain in 'Ant-Man'?",
      "correct_answer": "Yellowjacket (Darren Cross)",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Ghost (Ava Starr)", "Sonny Burch", "M.O.D.O.K."]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which powerful cosmic being is the father of Gamora and Nebula?",
      "correct_answer": "Thanos",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Collector", "Ego", "Ronan the Accuser"]
    },
    {
      "question": "On what planet did the Soul Stone reside?",
      "correct_answer": "Vormir",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Xandar", "Knowhere", "Morag"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the powerful substance the Red Skull seeks in 'Captain America: The First Avenger'?",
      "correct_answer": "The Tesseract",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Aether", "The Orb", "The Scepter"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of T'Challa's technologically gifted younger sister?",
      "correct_answer": "Shuri",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Okoye", "Nakia", "Ramonda"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which two original Avengers do not appear in 'Captain America: Civil War'?",
      "correct_answer": "Thor and Hulk",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Iron Man and Hawkeye", "Black Widow and Captain America", "Nick Fury and Maria Hill"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the treaty that regulates the activities of enhanced individuals?",
      "correct_answer": "The Sokovia Accords",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Registration Act", "The Avengers Initiative", "The Helicarrier Treaty"]
    },
    {
      "question": "In 'Thor: Ragnarok', what is the name of the planet Thor and Hulk are stranded on?",
      "correct_answer": "Sakaar",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Xandar", "Asgard", "Muspelheim"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who created Ultron?",
      "correct_answer": "Tony Stark and Bruce Banner",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Hank Pym", "Howard Stark", "Arnim Zola"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Doctor Strange's magical cloak?",
      "correct_answer": "The Cloak of Levitation",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Sorcerer's Shawl", "The Mantle of Mystery", "The Cape of Agamotto"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What species is Ronan the Accuser, the main villain of 'Guardians of the Galaxy'?",
      "correct_answer": "Kree",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Skrull", "Xandarian", "Chitauri"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the terrorist organization that kidnaps Tony Stark in the first 'Iron Man' movie?",
      "correct_answer": "The Ten Rings",
      "incorrect_answers": ["HYDRA", "The Hand", "A.I.M."]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these is NOT an alias used by Natasha Romanoff?",
      "correct_answer": "Sharon Carter",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Natalie Rushman", "Yelena Belova", "The Black Widow"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Hawkeye's real name?",
      "correct_answer": "Clint Barton",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Clint Eastwood", "Barton Fink", "Phil Coulson"]
    },
    {
      "question": "In 'Ant-Man and the Wasp', what realm are they trying to enter to rescue Janet van Dyne?",
      "correct_answer": "The Quantum Realm",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Negative Zone", "The Microverse", "The Astral Plane"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the rival company to Stark Industries, led by Justin Hammer?",
      "correct_answer": "Hammer Industries",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Roxxon Corporation", "Oscorp", "Pym Technologies"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the ruler of the Dark Dimension?",
      "correct_answer": "Dormammu",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Kaecilius", "Mephisto", "Surtur"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of particles allows for travel to the Quantum Realm?",
      "correct_answer": "Pym Particles",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Stark Particles", "Gamma Particles", "Beta Particles"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the alien race that Loki commands in 'The Avengers'?",
      "correct_answer": "The Chitauri",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Kree", "The Skrulls", "The Outriders"]
    },
    {
      "question": "In 'Black Panther', what is Erik Killmonger's primary motivation?",
      "correct_answer": "To use Wakanda's resources to liberate people of African descent worldwide",
      "incorrect_answers": ["To become rich", "To destroy Wakanda", "To challenge T'Challa for fun"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the primary antagonist in 'Spider-Man: Homecoming'?",
      "correct_answer": "The Vulture (Adrian Toomes)",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Mysterio (Quentin Beck)", "The Tinkerer", "Shocker"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the super-soldier program that created Captain America?",
      "correct_answer": "Project Rebirth",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Project Pegasus", "Weapon X", "Project Insight"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who guards the Soul Stone on Vormir?",
      "correct_answer": "Red Skull",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Collector", "The Watcher", "The Grandmaster"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the weapon forged for Thor in 'Avengers: Infinity War'?",
      "correct_answer": "Stormbreaker",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Mjolnir II", "Gungnir", "Thunderstrike"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Where does Peggy Carter work after WWII, as seen in her solo series?",
      "correct_answer": "SSR (Strategic Scientific Reserve)",
      "incorrect_answers": ["S.H.I.E.L.D.", "MI6", "CIA"]
    }
  ]